can you ever really go home again
or do you have to build your own home
what happens when things go back to
normal
we don't need things to go back to
normal we need a new normal
we're all looking for something some
truth some reality some honesty
that's right it's time to stop talking
it's time to start doing
but what what can one person do
well you can start by executive
producing my new show were you sitting
there the whole time
yep the man vulture caller got a radio
got a new show coming to comedy central
do you want to drive yeah but if we get
pulled over please let them know that i
identify as white
god okay so that you don't step in them
the god's honest truth will land
charlemagne mckelvey an
executive produced by stephen koviz
coming september 17th
to comedy central